God, that is the most beautiful
engagement ring ever.
Yeah, well, you should know.
You've bought, like,
a billion of them.
Yeah, you didn't get one.
Okay. Well,
tonight's the big night.
Hey, listen, how you
going to ask her?
It is going to be perfect.
I am taking her to her
favorite restaurant.
I'm going to get her
a bottle of the champagne
that she really loves therefore
knows how expensive it is.
Then, when the glasses are full
instead of proposing a toast,
I'm just going to propose.
Oh-h.
- It sounds perfect.
- Yeah.
You're going to mess it up.
Let me do it.
I'm not going to mess it up.
If she says no,
can I have the ring?
She's not going to say no.
If.
- Hey.
[muffled]
Hi, Monica.
- Give it.
- It's gone.
Phoebe.
[muffled]
Hey, Monica.
We're practically kissing.
[theme music]
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's DOA ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day your week ♪
♪ Your month
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me too ♪♪
- Hey.
Are any of you guys
free tonight?
My boss is hosting
this charity event
for underprivileged kids
and the more people I bring,
the better I look.
So, Monica, Chandler.
Well, Monica
and Chandler can't go.
We're going to dinner,
remember?
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
What's the big deal?
I just get mad when
Rachel doesn't remember
where we're going.
Where are you going?
- How about you guys?
- Open bar?
I think so.
I can do that for the kids.
Yeah, you know what?
I'll come, too.
I'm making money now.
It's about time
I give something back.
Well, you could also give back
the money you owe me.
Okay...have a benefit.
Hey.
Hey, Ross,
listen, can you
come to a charity event tonight?
Oh, no, I have plans
with Elizabeth.
Oh, so you're already
doing your part for the kids.
Sorry, it's just one
of our last nights together
before she leaves for camp
to be a counselor.
Ross, let me ask
you a question.
All jokes aside, where is
this relationship going?
Wait a minute.
All jokes aside?
I didn't agree to that.
Do you really see this
as a long-term thing?
I don't know.
You know, you are
12 years older than her.
Wait a minute, d-does everyone
feel this way?
- Yeah.
- Sort of.
- Yeah,
- Sorry.
Oh, wow, uh.
I thought you guys
were like just making jokes.
I had no idea.
Well, you know what?
You guys are wrong.
Yes, there is a chronological
age difference
but I never notice it.
You know why?
Because she is very mature.
Besides, it doesn't
really matter to me
what you guys think.
I mean I'm the one
dating Elizabeth, not you.
Not what she said last night.
Yeah. See, now,
he could date her.
Will you marry me?
Hey, you marry me.
What's going on,
Little Elves?
It's the big night.
We wanted to wish you good luck.
Yeah, yeah. You
have the ring?
Yeah, right here
in my pocket.
Oh.
- Pheebs.
- What? Oh. O-op.
Okay, now, will you
guys get out of here?
I want this to
be a surprise
and she's
going to know.
Yeah, yeah, you guys,
get out of here.
Hey. Hi, guys.
- You look beautiful.
- Mm. Thank you.
What's going on?
We're just really ex..
...excited about this
charity event
that we have to go to.
- Here.
- Oh, thank you.
So, now, what's
going on here?
Uh, well, uh, this
is a silent auction.
They lay out
all the stuff here
and then you write
down your offer
and then the highest bid
gets it.
No, I know what
a silent auction is.
I meant, what's going
on with your hair?
Uh, w-why?
No, it's nice.
- Nice to see you, Rachel.
- Oh.
So glad you brought someone.
Oh, someone?
I brought people.
Mr. Thompson,
this is Phoebe.
Phoebe, this is Mr. Thompson.
He's the head
of my department.
And I also
brought my friend Joey.
Oh, shrimp toast.
Uh, you know,
I-I don't know where he is.
Well, I hope you're going to bid
on some things, Rachel.
Well, you know what,
actually I was about to bid
on this lovely trip to Paris.
- Oh, nice choice.
- Yeah.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Ha. Okay.
Twenty dollars.
Shut the door, shut the door.
W-What's going on?
The guys across the hall are
throwing water balloons at us.
Oh, you have to call the police.
That's what I did
to the kids in my building.
No, it's a water
balloon fight.
- We started it.
- Oh. Um...mmm.
Listen, um, I,
I-I just stopped by
to see if you wanted
to see this play tonight.
Um...it's supposed
to be excellent.
The director is--
Who drank all
the kamikazes?
Nobody. We put 'em in here!
[squealing]
- You want some?
- No.
Okay, okay. Okay.
Okay. Look,
can I, can I just
just talk to you
for a second?
Yeah, sure.
Um, so this play, um
what do you think?
I-It's gotten great reviews,
you know the--
Attack!
[girls screaming]
Put your balloons down.
You put your balloons down.
You put yours..
Everybody! Put their
balloons down!
Now, this is a nice suit.
Our next item is the romantic
trip to Paris.
It goes to Emil Alexander,
with a high bid of $2,300.
Oh. So close.
Heya, guys, look.
I got me some drinks.
What are you doing?
Open bar.
And finally our biggest item
of the night.
The 22-foot gentleman's
daysailer sailboat.
The winning bid
was a whopping $20,000.
O-oh.
I won.
That was my guess.
What? What? What?
I guessed $20,000.
Joey, it is an auction.
You don't guess,
you buy.
What?
I don't have $20,000.
Congratulations on
your new boat, Joey Tribbiani.
Joey, sit down.
Forget her.
You enjoy this.
Wow. Wow.
[sighing]
What are you doing?
One nation, under God
indivisible with liberty
and justice for all.
[chuckling]
I remembered it.
The champagne is here.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, yes, I'm good.
Are you good? Are you good?
Is everything, are you
are y-you perfect, perfect?
Yeah. I'm okay.
I'm actually, I'm
a little cold, though.
Can I, can I have your jacket?
Oh, yeah.
Uh, no, you can't
have my jacket.
Because then I
would be cold.
If you thought that you
were going to be cold
you should have brought
your own jacket.
But, uh, other than
that are you okay?
Are you okay?
[chuckling]
You're sure you're okay?
Yes. I'm fine.
In fact, I've been fine
for a long time now
and I think...the reason is you.
Mm, that's sweet.
Okay, um.
[clearing throat]
Before I met you,
I had really little life
and I couldn't imagine
growing old with--
Oh, my God.
I know, but just
let me say it.
Oh, my God, Richard.
What? I'm Chandler.
Oh, that's Richard.
Oh, God. Maybe he won't see us.
Richard!
Monica. Chandler.
Hey, hey.
I don't know
why I did that.
Hey, it, it's good to see you.
You, too. You let
your hair grow long.
Yeah, oh, that's right
you, you always
wanted me to.
I see you got
your mustache back.
Well, my nose got lonely.
And, uh, you don't
have a mustache
which is good.
I'm Chandler, I make jokes
when I'm uncomfortable.
Oh, I'm sorry. Lisa.
Monica, Chandler.
We used to date.
Richard, no one's
supposed to know about us.
See, I did it again.
Chandler, w-why
don't we sit down.
Yeah, I'll sit down.
It's good to see you.
Your table's ready, sir.
- Oh. Good to see you guys.
- Yes.
Or, if you prefer
this table's available.
That might be fun.
What were you thinking?
I didn't know
it was an auction.
I figured
I'd take a guess.
Help a charity, free boat.
Why would a charity
give away a free boat?
I don't know...charity?
Oh.
Oh, just buy the damn boat.
Phoebe, don't you think
you've had enough to drink?
I'm just helping the kids.
How is you drinking
helping the kids?
Because the more I drink
the less there is
for the kids to drink.
- Mr. Tribbiani.
- Oh, hey.
Your generous contribution
brings us a big step closer
to building the youth center.
Just out of curiosity
how, how much
is that boat worth?
I think it was valued
at $19,000.
I was pretty close.
Uh...so, bad news.
Um...I can't
buy the boat.
I don't have any money.
[stifling laughter]
Joey...Joey, good one.
You're silly.
[laughing]
Very good. Very good.
So, uh, listen I think
I'm going to take off now.
Hey, y-you cannot
leave, Joey.
You agreed to buy
that boat, alright?
It is a contract.
Plus, if you leave,
my boss is going to kill me.
What am I going
to do, Rach?
I don't have
that kind of money.
I know. Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Alright, alright. This is what
we're going to do.
We are going to go
to the next highest bidder
and we are just going
to let them buy it
and then you're just
going to pay the difference.
Okay, look, I don't know
why the kids need
a youth center anyway, you know?
They should just watch TV
after school, like I did
and I turned out fine.
Not great.
So we're hiding
in the bathroom..
And then I sneak out
but, before Monica can,
her parents come in.
Yeah, so I hide in the shower
and, the next thing you know
they're going at it
right on the bathroom floor.
[laughing]
Oh, my God.
I got a good one.
I once walked in on
both my parents
making love to the same guy.
It's so great seeing
you guys again.
I'd like to make a toast.
Uh...as a poet
once said
"in the sweetness
of friendship
"let there be laughter
and sharing of pleasures
"for in the dew
of little things
"the heart
finds its morning
and is refreshed."
Oh.
What?
Oh, my God. You guys.
Before you say anything
have we got
a story for you.
Guess who we bumped
into at dinner.
- Who?
- Richard.
Who? Oh.
Oh!
I thought you were
going out with Elizabeth.
Yeah, I was, but she was
a little busy
with a water
balloon fight.
Oh, Ross, sometimes,
grownups have commitments
they just can't get out of.
You know, maybe she
is too young for me.
When I was over there
and she was
running around with her friends
I felt like I was a baby-sitter.
I finally started to see
what you guys
were talking about.
I don't know what to do.
Why don't you
just weigh out
the good stuff about
the relationship
against the bad stuff?
I mean that's what I did
when I first started..
...weighing stuff.
Okay, bad stuff:
Well, I'm-I'm 12 years older
than she is.
If the school finds
out, you're fired.
She's leaving
for three months.
For camp.
Okay, good stuff.
Um...well, she's...she's
sweet and pretty and..
Look, Ross, the only
question you need to ask
is do you see a future?
I mean, like, do you see
yourself marrying her?
Oh, my God,
you did it already.
You married her,
didn't you?
No, no, I didn't do that.
It's just..
Okay, honestly, no.
I don't...I don't see
a big future with her.
Okay, well, I-I think
that's your answer.
I got to talk to her.
Oh, I hate this part.
You have to forget
about Elizabeth.
I mean, if you're not careful
you may not get married
at all this year.
Rachel, Rachel.
Okay, the next highest bidder
is at table one.
- Oh, great.
- Yeah.
Oh, and the guy who got the
Paris trip is at table four.
Oh, okay.
Why do you care about the guy
who won the Paris trip?
It's a trip for two.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, is the person who won
the Paris trip at this table?
- That was me.
- Oh. Enchante.
Uh...excuse me.
Is there a Mr. Bowmont
at this table?
- That's me.
- Oh, yeah.
Well, hello.
This is your
lucky day, Mr. Bowmont.
The gentleman daysailer
has just become
available again.
And I believe that you made
a bid of $18,000.
Y-You have to pay that.
It's not just a guess.
Okay.
I was actually
relieved, uh
I didn't win the boat.
My wife would have killed me.
Are you kidding me?
She's going to love this boat.
- Yeah. What's your wife's name?
- It's Pam.
Pam. Oh, God. Just imagine
this, the Pam.
Oh...ho-ho.
I don't think she'd like that.
Okay, i-imagine this,
the Mr. Bowmont.
O-oh.
I don't think so, dear.
Okay, look, let me paint
you a little picture.
Alright, you are
setting sail up the Hudson.
You got the wind
in your ha-arms.
You, you get all
the peace and quiet
that you've always wanted.
You get back to nature.
You can go fishing.
You c-can get one
of those little hats
and have people
call you "captain."
And then, when you're old,
"cappy."
What the hell. It's for
a good cause. Alright.
No way. It's mine.
What? What?
All that stuff you
just said, I want that!
Joey, you don't
have $20,000.
Who cares?
I'll make payments.
Whatever it takes.
I want the Mr. Bowmont.
Oh, my God, you're back.
Oh, let me see it.
Let me see your hand.
Why do you want
to see my hand?
I want to see
what's in your hand.
I want to see the trash.
Ew-w. O-oh,
it's all dirty.
- You should throw this out.
- Yeah.
Okay.
What did you
guys just do?
What happened?
Richard was there,
so I couldn't do it.
- Oh, no.
- Oh.
I was going to do it tomorrow,
you know, and surprise her.
- But now you've ruined it.
- Oh, we didn't ruin it.
Who walks into a room and asks
to see a person's hands?
Well, a palm reader,
a manicurist
a hand doctor.
Glove salesman.
Good one. Yeah.
This is terrible.
What am I going to do?
Look, she only suspects
something, okay?
She doesn't know for sure
so just throw her
off the track.
That's right. I could
throw her off.
I could make her think that, uh
marriage was the last thing
on my mind.
Yeah, convince her t-that
you're scared of commitment.
I can do that.
I've had 30 years of practice.
Hey, being you
is finally going to pay off.
Oh, I had to go all the way
to the basement
because some idiot keeps
stuffing the trash chute
with pizza boxes.
That guy still doing that? Huh.
Hey. Oh, my God, you're here.
- Let me see your hand.
- No, you're too late.
She already took
out the trash.
[Ross thinking] Wow.
I have never had
such a healthy breakup.
She was such
a grownup about it.
She didn't seem too
immature for me.
Did I just make a huge mistake?
Ross, wait.
Elizabeth...thank God.
I was just thinking about--
You suck!
What?
Okay.
Breakup's still on.
Okay, okay, here she comes.
How do I look?
Do I look like a guy
who doesn't want to get married?
Yeah. And also
a little like a French guy.
I never noticed
that before.
Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- What are you up to?
- Oh, just hanging out.
Talking about websites.
Yeah.
Yeah, we saw this really
interesting website
about marriage and how totally
unnecessary it is
and how it's just a way for the
government to keep tabs on you.
Yeah. Big brother.
Well, that's a little crazy.
Although I am,
you know, glad to hear
that you're branching out
on what you
look at on the internet.
You know, it just
got me thinking, though.
Why would anybody ever
want to get married, huh?
Why? To celebrate
your relationship.
To solidify your commitment.
To declare your love for one
another to the world.
Eh.
Okay, well,
that's good to know.
Ah. The Mr. Bowmont's here!
Hey, Monica, there's a
customer who wants
to compliment the chef.
- Shall I let him in?
- Sure. I love this part.
Come on in.
Hi.
Richard.
Actually, I'm not here
to compliment the chef.
Oh, that's okay.
I hate when people come back
to compliment the chef.
Like I have
nothing better to do.
So what's up?
Well, it was great seeing you
the other night.
Yeah, it was good
to see you, too.
Did you come down here
to tell me that?
No. I came here
to tell you something else.
I came here
to tell you I still love you.
[theme music]